Abdulrasheed Ibrahim



abdulrasheedibrahim47@gmail.com



+2347033389645



linkedin.com/in/abdulrasheed-ibrahim-2b3a90103 https://abdull.dev/



Summary

Professional Software Engineer, Skilled in React.js, React Native, Next.js, Redux, Python, Django, Flask, PostgreSQL, GCP, and AWS.

I'm an experienced web and mobile developer with six years of experience, throughout years of my experience, I've built, deployed, and maintained several software solutions that aids to meet consumer's business requirements as well as increase productivity for various organizations.

Those solutions range from native Android and iOS applications, hybrid applications to web and desktop solutions.

Experience



Javascript Developer

Carilo

Mar 2020 - Present (1 year 6 months +)

Carilo is a way billing react native mobile application that I and a team are working on in our free time.

My primary role at Carilo has being to design, build, and maintain both the android and iOS versions of our product. I also do contribute to the backend from time to time.

Python Developer

Carilo

Mar 2020 - Present (1 year 6 months +)

Worked with Django, Django Rest Framework, Django Channels, and AWS.

As a Python Web Developer (Using Django), I do partake in the development of our backend API which uses Django Rest Framework.

Full Stack Engineer

Bitpoint Nigeria Limited

Jun 2018 - Present (3 years 3 months +)

Lead developer at Bitpoint Nigeria Limited. Worked on Bitsmss, an enterprise multi-tenant school management software in Nigeria.

My role at Bitpoint has being to perform code reviews before they get merged into our codebase, write quality code, mentor, guide others, and manage our DevOps operations which includes deploying and maintaining product versions on AWS Elastic Beanstalk with Celery to handle queues.

Education

Modibbo Adama University Of Technology, YOLA

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology 2015 - 2020

Licenses & Certifications

- The Ultimate React Native Series: Fundamentals Code With Mosh cert_2rqxwjwg
- The Ultimate React Native Series: Advanced Concepts Code With Mosh cert_qn0wz0gm

Skills

React Native • React.js • Redux.js • Next.js • Python (Programming Language) • Django • Flask • SQL • Google Cloud Platform (GCP) • PostgreSQL

Honors & Awards

ND - Information Technology - Mautech Yola
Jun 2016